

# DANE KILPATRICK FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

### SKILLS

Javascript React Git/Github Node.js HTML Express CSS MongoDB jQuery **PSQL** Bootstrap Python Materialize Django

# PROFILE

I am an adaptable and creative web developer. I pursue collaborative projects that have a meaningful and impactful outcome on everyday life. I utilize my experience in the Air Force and technology sales to help resolve current problems in the most efficient way possible. I have a passion for the aesthetic side of web development that impacts the overall experience of the user.

# SOCIAL



www.DaneKilpatrick.com



✓ Dkilpatrick1990@Gmail.com



Linkedin.com/in/danekilpatrick



803-931-6992

# PROJECTS

Adopt A Woof | CRUD app built in Python with DjangoDB

Happy Hour | A happy hour locator app using Express, NodeJS and MongoDB

Tic Tac Toe | Used Javascript to create functional Tic Tac Toe game

GeoQuakes | Earthquake tracking app using Jquery and Google Maps API

Neon Drummer | A web application utilizing ES6, where you use the keyboard keys A - L to make beats.

Google Landing Page | Built with HTML, CSS and JavaScript

K.I.W | The New Yorker mock-up with just HTML, CSS and JavaScript. This will later be refractored with React.

# EXPERIENCE

# Insight | Account Executive

2017 - 2018

- Consulted potential clients on streamlining and modernizing their current IT environment by utilizing hardware, software, and service solutions from over 5000 partners
- Compensated solely on profitability of each deal versus total revenue, with control of gross profit.
- Required to bring in at least 3 net new clients per quarter

#### United States Air Force | Surveillance Technician

2013 - 2015

- Part of a global team using the BC3T radar systems to detect and identify in friendly and combat air spaces and performed 864 Command and Control hours.
- Provided Combat Identifications for over 8000 missions in Afghanistan, Iraq and the Arabian Gulf.
- Prepared the duty and training schedule for 77 coalition personnel which included 14 crew positions/56 shifts daily and assisted in 35 High-Value Airborne Asset ISIL/Taliban Target Strikes.

# EDUCATION | TRAINING

2017 - 2017 **Web Development Immersive** General Assembly

Air and Space Operations Technology 2013 - 2015

Keesler AFB, Luke AFB, Spangdahlem AB **General Studies** 2009 - 2011

Holmes Community College